improvephotography.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy | Improve Photography

At Improve Photography, LLC we are committed to providing you with a safe, fun, and informative website, without the worry of your personal information being used inapppropriately.  While you are on ImprovePhotography.com, some information is gathered about you.  This information, which is typical of most websites, helps us to know how many people visit the site and how we can best serve you.

Our Privacy Policy is explained below.  This Privacy Policy may be update frequently, so if you are extraordinarily sensitive about data collection, you may want to keep checking back.

 **1.  Information We Collect from You**

Data can be collected and processed when our website is in operation by you. The following are approved methods of collection:

1.1 If you register for information or complete a purchase, by filling out a form we can collect the information provided.  Improve Photography LLC does not store any credit card information, only your Paypal email address.  We never see your credit card information, only Paypal does.

1.2 Traffic data, weblogs, location data, and any other communication can be collected.  These details come from your visit to our site and any resource tools you use while on the site.

1.3 Any communication on our website or to Improve Photography LLC staff or its assigns. This includes contact forms on the site, email communication, commenting on the website, etc.

 **2.  Use of Cookies**

Circumstances may arise when we may need to gather information about your computer to help provide appropriate services or products to you or to prevent SPAM.  This information may be shared with advertisers on Improve Photography.

Cookies are used to collect general statistics about the type of users of this website.  We may use cookies to improve your experience, but if you are sensitive about cookies, you can simply block them on any modern web browser.

If our advertisers use cookies it will result from a click on their ad, so if you want to prevent advertiser cookies, simply avail yourself of the “block cookies” feature of your web browser.

 **3.  Use of Your Personal Information**

3.1 Any commitment we make on a contracted basis with you or with others.

3.2 If information is requested from Improve Photography concerning services or products that we offer, we may use your personal information.

3.3 Notification re- changes or improvements may be sent to you in regards to product or service changes that could affect our service to you.

3.4 Existing customers can be contacted on the topic of photography goods or services related to a previous sale, if we feel you might be interested in additional books, apps, or other photography products.

3.5 Added use of your data may include permission for third parties to use your data.  This permission would be granted by you in regards to unrelated products or services that may be in your interests.  We or third parties can only contact you in regards to this information if consent has been provided for information collection.

3.6 Personally identifiable data about you, which could be used to disclose your identity, is never shared with third parties without your consent.

 **4.  Storing Your Personal Data**

4.1 Your data is safely secured in encrypted locations around the world.

4.2 Secured servers are used by our company to ensure proper data storage.  Information on transactions is kept encrypted for safety measures.

4.3 Transmission of data on the internet is inherently insecure.  We do not and cannot guarantee security of information collected electronically or transmitted; however, we take reasonable steps to provide security.  As a result of our inability to guarantee safety, you are submitting information to us at your own risk.  The only way to be truly safe is to not transmit any data to Improve Photography LLC.

 **5.  Disclosing Your Information**

5.1 Personal information to third parties may be disclosed:

5.2 This disclosure occurs when we sell all or a section of our business or assets to a third party.

5.2.1 Personal information can be offered to any member of our company, such as subsidiaries, holding companies and their subsidiaries only if deemed appropriate.

5.2.2 Legal requirements may force us to share your information.

5.2.3 Lowering credit risk and fraud protection may result in information disclosure.

 **6.  Third Party Links**

Links might be discovered on our site that direct you to third parties.  You should check their terms of use and privacy policy.  We do not accept liability or responsibility for their privacy policies or their actions.

 **7.  Contacting Improve Photography LLC**

We may be contacted by emailing support@improvephotography.com.

## Advertising Privacy Statement

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative's multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at support@improvephotography.com and contact AdThrive at [info@adthrive.com](mailto:info@adthrive.com). If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)
